VA: Hello. This is Jenny from CarMax Auto Finance calling you with an important message.
VA: May I speak with Graham?
Graeme: That's me.
VA: For your security, may I confirm your date of birth, please?
Graeme: July twenty one nineteen fifty eight.
VA: Great. And your ZIP code?
Graeme: My ZIP code is seven five zero two five.
VA: Great.
VA: I've successfully verified your identity.
VA: Graham, I see that your account has a past due balance of one thousand seven hundred eighty dollars and seventy cents, originally due on August twenty fifth twenty twenty five.
VA: You are currently about seventeen days past due.
VA: Please note, this is an attempt to collect a debt, and any information obtained will be used for debt collection purpose only.
VA: Would you like to take care of this payment now?
Graeme: I've fallen behind on my payments, and I'm having trouble making payment on time.
VA: Okay.
VA: Could you let me know the future date that works for you to schedule your promise to pay?
Graeme: Yeah. Can I pay by the twenty fifth of September?
VA: Great news.
VA: As a onetime courtesy, I can move your payment to twenty fifth of September.
VA: Would you like me to go ahead and reschedule this for you?
Graeme: Yes, please.
VA: Excellent.
VA: I've updated your payment schedule.
VA: Remember, it's important to stick to this new plan.
VA: If anything comes up, just reach out to us in advance to avoid any issues with late fees. Do you need any further assistance today?
Graeme: No. That's it. Thanks.
VA: Thank you for reaching out to CarMax.
VA: We wish you a wonderful day.